[
    {
        "question": "I'll be there for you, when the rain starts to _____",
        "answer1": "fall",
        "answer2": "pour",
        "answer3": "lash",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The license plate said fresh and it had _____ in the mirror",
        "answer1": "dice",
        "answer2": "mice",
        "answer3": "rice",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Hanging out down the _____, the same old thing we did last week",
        "answer1": "beach",
        "answer2": "street",
        "answer3": "block",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "But I can't do this all on my own, no, I know, I'm no ______",
        "answer1": "superman",
        "answer2": "doctor",
        "answer3": "actor",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sometimes you want to go where everybody knows your _____",
        "answer1": "age",
        "answer2": "story",
        "answer3": "name",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Maths, science, history, unraveling the mysteries that all started with a big _____",
        "answer1": "bang",
        "answer2": "noise",
        "answer3": "boom",
        "correctAnswer": 1 
    },
    {
        "question": "Scooby-Dooby-Doo, where are you? We got some _____ to do now",
        "answer1": "jobs",
        "answer2": "stuff",
        "answer3": "work",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Then drop on the deck and flop like a _____, Spongebob Squarepants!",
        "answer1": "fish",
        "answer2": "sponge",
        "answer3": "star",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Pokemon! Oh, you're my best friend, in a world we must _____!",
        "answer1": "destroy",
        "answer2": "defend",
        "answer3": "understand",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Catches _____ just like flies. Look out! Here comes the Spider-Man.",
        "answer1": "dreams",
        "answer2": "bees",
        "answer3": "thieves",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    }
]